marcos.com 2019-09-04

# Privacy Policy | Marcos.com

Marco’s Franchising, LLC and its affiliates (“Marco’s”) is committed to protecting and safeguarding the privacy of your personal information on this website located at www.marcos.com and any other online and mobile websites, blogs, social media pages, and mobile applications operated by Marco’s Franchising, LLC on behalf of itself and its affiliates and franchisees (collectively, for purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Marco’s,” “we” or “us”) (collectively, the “Site”) (unless a different policy is provided on a particular site or application, in which case such different policy shall control). It is important for you to know how we treat your personal information and ask that you read the following policy. The terms of this Privacy Policy apply to all users of this Site. Below you will find answers to several questions regarding our Privacy Policy. If you have questions about our policy, [please click here](https://cms.marcos.com/customer-contact-center) to complete our electronic feedback form.

## WHAT INFORMATION DOES MARCO’S COLLECT ON ME AND HOW IS IT USED?

Marco’s collects information from various sources including information that our customers supply to us via electronic mail or on social media, information we collect from users of our website, and various other sources of information provided to us. This information is collected electronically on all users of our website, including customers, by means of cookies. The personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) collected on this Site can include some or all of the following: your name, address, telephone number(s), e-mail addresses, text messaging information and other contact information associated with electronic or digital messaging methods, vehicles and interaction, credit card information, demographic information, and any other information you may voluntarily provide. You will have the choice whether or not to disclose such Personal Information in the above activities; however, some parts of the Site and some services may be more difficult or impossible to use if you choose not to disclose Personal Information.

Personal Information is used to send you special advertisements, offers and notices regarding our products and restaurants. This includes communications via email, mail, and/or digital marketing platforms. We also use this information to contact you concerning any problems or delays with your order, your overall level of satisfaction with our products and services, or otherwise communicate with you concerning your relationship with us.

In addition to the Personal Information identified above, our web servers automatically identify computers by their IP addresses. We may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users’ movement and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. To clarify, IP addresses are not linked to Personal Information.

Further, our Site may use technologies such as “cookies” to provide visitors with tailored information upon each visit. Cookies are a common part of many commercial websites that allow small text files to be sent by a website, accepted by a web browser and then placed on your hard drive as recognition for repeat visits to the Site. Every time you visit our Site, our servers, through cookies, pixels and/or GIF files, collect basic technical information such as your domain name, the address of the last URL visited prior to clicking through to the Site, and your browser and operating system. You do not need to enable cookies to visit our Site; however, some parts of the Site and some services may be more difficult or impossible to use if cookies are disabled. To clarify, cookies are not linked to any Personal Information you provide us while on this Site.

## HOW DOES MARCO’S STORE THE INFORMATION IT COLLECTS?

We store the information you provide to us and the information we collect electronically in our computer databases. We own, maintain and operate our computer servers containing our databases. Access to our computer servers is controlled by firewalls and security gatekeepers.

## WITH WHOM DOES MARCO’S SHARE INFORMATION?

Marco’s may share Personal Information with our franchisees and restaurant affiliates so that your local Marco’s Pizza store can better serve you. We do not, however, sell or provide Personal Information to outside parties. Please note that this does not include Marco’s trusted third party vendors who assist us in operating our website and conducting our business in general. We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information only with your written consent or when it has been determined appropriate in order to comply with law.

How can I stop receiving notices about future offers or to stop my personal information from being shared? For those who initially opted-in to receive future offers or promotional materials or to allow the sharing of Personal Information may subsequently opt-out as follows: For email communications: (a) send an e-mail to [eclub@marcos.com](mailto:eclub@marcos.com) or (b) if you are a registered user, you may choose to opt-out of future email by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our email.

## DOES THE MARCO’S SITE LINK TO OTHER’S WEBSITES?

Our Site may link to other websites not maintained by or related to Marco’s. Any hyperlinks located on our website are provided as a service to our users and the linked websites are not necessarily sponsored by or affiliated with Marco’s in any way. We are not responsible for, nor do we make representations or warranties on the content of any other website. Any such hyperlinks are to be accessed at the user’s own risk.

## HOW DOES MARCO’S HANDLE CHILDREN’S PRIVACY ONLINE?

Online ordering, customer registration for on-line ordering, and customer feedback pages of this website are directed toward and designed for use by persons aged 13 or older. We do not establish or maintain registrations for any child whom we know to be under the age of 13. We do not solicit or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If we discover that we have received personally identifiable information from an individual who indicates that he or she is, or whom we otherwise have reason to believe is, under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our systems.

### Our policies may change.

This is our current privacy policy, but we reserve the right to change this policy and our website at any time. You should review this privacy policy periodically. If our policies regarding collection, storage and use of your information change, the information collected under prior policies will continue to be governed by those policies, unless we obtain your consent to use that information in new ways.

Please contact us with any questions or comments. If you believe that a violation of this policy may have occurred, please let us know. Our complete contact information is provided on the Customer Feedback link on our website at [www.marcos.com/customer-feedback](https://cms.marcos.com/customer-contact-center) or you may contact us directly at (800) 262-7267.
